getsync.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Resilio

#### **Date of last revision: May 24, 2018**

Resilio, Inc. ( **“Resilio”** ) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our websites ( **“Sites”** ), applications and services (collectively, the **“Services”** ). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform visitors to the Sites and users of the Services how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled **“Questions? Contact Us”** at the end of this privacy policy.In this Privacy Policy, Resilio’s software called the “Resilio Client” application or the “Resilio Connect” application are sometimes collectively referred to hereunder as the “Resilio Client.” Resilio’s other applications, including, but not limited to, Connect Management Console and Connect Agents, are sometimes referred to hereunder as “Resilio’s Other Applications.” The Resilio Clients and Resilio’s Other Applications are sometimes collectively referred to as the “Software”.  

### What information does Resilio, Inc. collect and how does Resilio use it?

#### **How the Resilio Client Works**

Resilio software (the **“Resilio Client”** ) is a software application on your machine that manages downloads. It downloads files quickly by trading pieces with other users who are also downloading (or have downloaded) the same content. Your use of the Resilio Client to download files will, in turn, enable other Resilio users to download pieces of those files from you. Although your IP address is associated with your piece of the file, other users will not have access to any other personal information about you.We do not track which files you transfer with the Resilio Client. Merely using the Resilio Client does not cause a record of which files you transfer to be kept by Resilio or Resilio on behalf of any third party.  

#### **Gathering and Use of Non-personally Identifiable Information**

Each time a visitor comes to one of our Sites, we collect some limited information that your browser routinely makes available whenever you visit a website. We collect this data to improve the overall quality of the online experience, including product monitoring, and product improvement. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.In addition to collecting these types of information, Resilio collects aggregate queries for internal reporting and targeted advertising. We also count, track, and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our websites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the websites, etc.). Resilio will not disclose your individual identity or personal data without your permission.In the event that you provide us with answers to voluntary survey questions, we may present this information to our partners, in the form of grouped statistics compiled from our users’ answers to such questions.We also aggregate some data from the Resilio Client regarding total traffic flows and content delivery performance as well as other data collected in the use of our products or services in order to understand usability and monitor network conditions and compare the performance of Resilio and HTTP protocols on the public internet.We may also receive and collect information from your computer and browser, Resilio cookie information and software and hardware attributes. Additionally we may also collect information about your computer or mobile device, such as your device model, browser type, or sensors in your device like the accelerometer. Resilio uses such information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.  

#### **Gathering and Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

You may visit the Sites and use the Resilio Client and many of the Services without any registration at all. However, from time to time, we may enable certain additional functionality or services whereby you will have to create a user account, and we may collect and process the following information about you:  

  * information such as your name, address, phone number and e-mail address, and other demographic information (such as date of birth, gender, age, and interests) that you provide by completing forms on the Sites, including if you register as a user of the Services, subscribe to our mailing lists, upload or submit any material through the services, or request any information.  

  * your log-in and password details in connection with the account sign-in process;  

  * details of any requests or transactions made by you through the Service;  

  * communications you send to us, for example to report a problem or to submit queries, concerns, or comments regarding the Service or its content;  

  * information that you post to the Site in the form of comments or contributions to discussions; and IP addresses.  

#### **We will use the personal information you provide to:**

  * identify you when you sign-in to your account;  

  * enable us to provide you with the Services or to carry out your instructions (for example, to process payment information);send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us;  

  * present projects to you when you use the Service which we believe will be of interest based on your geographic location and previous use of the Service;  

  * administer your account with us;  

  * enable us to contact you regarding any question you make through the Service;  

  * analyze the use of the Service and the people visiting to improve our content and Services; and use for other purposes that we may disclose to you when we request your information.  

We may also use e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information from time to time in order to gather and provide to our members and visitors improved content and features.

When you provide payment data, we will store that data to help you complete future transactions when logged into your account, and you agree that (i) we have permission to retain the payment information and method, including all submitted debit and credit card information, submitted by you and your issuing bank or the applicable payment network; and (ii) we or our reseller (as applicable) are authorized to charge you for the subscriptions you select using the established payment method and the information you provide that is stored in your account as of the applicable date for payment.  You may remove the payment instrument information associated with your Sync account by contacting us at <https://help.resilio.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=91563>. 

After you close your account or remove a payment instrument, however, Resilio will retain your payment instrument data for as long as reasonably necessary to complete your existing transaction, to comply with legal and reporting requirements, and for the detection and prevention of fraud.

Notwithstanding any other term of this Privacy Policy, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

#### Does Resilio use "cookies"?

Cookies are tiny text files that are stored on a user’s browser. Most cookies contain a unique identifier called a cookie ID: a string of characters that websites and servers associate with the browser on which the cookie is stored. This allows websites and servers to distinguish the browser from other browsers that store different cookies, and to recognize each browser by its unique cookie ID. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor's individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time. Third party analytics, ad-serving and affiliate partners may set or have cookies set and access their cookies or local storage objects on your computer, when you are using the Resilio Client or visiting a Resilio website and may collect information about your online activities across websites or online services. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access many, if not all, of the features of the Resilio websites or the Resilio Client. However, some parts of the Resilio websites or the Resilio Client may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads for Resilio.com on other sites. Google’s use of cookies enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Resilio.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>[  
](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
Resilio also uses 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system. The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. – Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service.

You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. Also, you can opt out of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

We may utilize Google Analytics Suite in the collection, compilation and analysis of information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on some of our Services, and to develop website content. This analytics data is not tied to any Personal Information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ . You can opt out of Google’s collection and Processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

#### Does Resilio disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?

Resilio does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide for Resilio in any registration or use of the Resilio websites or the Resilio Client, except when it’s necessary to provide the Services (like when we partner with payment processors). This information is used to better understand visitors’ use of the features of the Resilio websites or the Resilio Client, to support related transactions made on or through the Resilio websites or the Resilio Client, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, advertisement or other notifications to them. However, this data in an aggregate form without any personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Should you no longer wish to receive information from us, or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal data you gave us. You can do this simply by contacting us in any of the simple ways set forth below in the section entitled **“How do you change the information we have for you?”

‍

**Finally, we may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our assets or equity securities or upon any other corporate reorganization.  

#### Resilio’s special note to parents

In compliance with the 1998 Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), the Sites are general audience websites, and do not knowingly collect, nor will it ever knowingly retain, personally identifiable information from any visitor Resilio actually knows to be under thirteen years of age without the consent of that child's parent or legal guardian.  

#### How do you change the information we have for you?

To update or modify the information that we have on file for your user account, simply go to the applicable Site or Service, log in, go to the user account section, then modify your details and settings as necessary.  

#### Third party links and co-brand relationships

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites or services to link to, and/or frame within, the Sites or Services. We may also include offers from third parties as part of the installation process for our software. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these third party sites or services, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our Site or Services) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites or services. These linked sites or services are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.  

#### Notification of changes

By visiting the website or using the applications and/or services, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  

#### Questions? Contact us

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please do not hesitate to write to us at:  
‍  
 **Privacy Matters**  
c/o Resilio, Inc. 59 Grant Ave, Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94108

 **You can also file a ticket with support by going to:**  
<https://help.resilio.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=91563> and use subject “Privacy” or GDPR (if question/comment is GDPR related)
